The much loved Australian story of an outback family and a
Christmas adventure that they would never forget.
Bush Christmas is a family, adventure, drama film directed by Henri Safran.
In the Australian outback a family struggles to keep its farm from foreclosure.
Their only hope is that their horse, Prince, will
win money in a New Year's race.
But when Prince is stolen the children embark on a
dangerous and exciting adventure to get him back.
Bill, played by John Ewart.
Sly, played by John Howard.
John Thompson, played by Mark Spain.
Helen, played by Nicole Kidman.
Ben Thompson, played by Peter Sumner.
Manalpuy, played by Manalpuy.
Bush Christmas (also known as Prince and the Great Race) is a 1983 Australian
Christmas drama film and a remake of the 1947 film of the same name.
The film marked actress Nicole Kidman's first feature film role.
It was filmed on location on the Lamington Plateau, Queensland.
It is also notable for music by the Bushwackers.
The film explores themes of horse race, money problems,
rustlers, christmas, australian bush.
The tone is emotional.